<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>index on wooper blog</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/</link><description>Recent content in index on wooper blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 Kaz Bishop</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 17:44:06 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.kazam.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cracking Legacy Passwords</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/cracking-passwords-aws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/cracking-passwords-aws/</guid><description>The advent of cloud computing and ephemeral compute has to be one of the greatest things that ever happened to password cracking. Gone are the days of needing to buy an insane GPU rig, spend many to hours build it out, and have it be obsolete by the end of the year.
Unfortunately, the state of password cracking also hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed very much in many years. Hashcat is still the king, rainbow tables are still the most effective method of looking things up, and to my knowledge there are no projects that exist to make deployment, cracking, and infra termination all happen in a single step.</description></item><item><title>Proxmox Notes</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/proxmox-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/proxmox-notes/</guid><description>Collection of proxmox notes
MacOS virt-viewer (SPICE) Unfortunately it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like virt-viewer is supported by default for macos, so you have to use a 3P homebrew formula to get this working. The following gist was helpful in setup:
https://gist.github.com/tomdaley92/789688fc68e77477d468f7b9e59af51c
Note that you no-longer need to install the tap as the formula is in homebrew proper now.
I had to chown a folder of icons used by this formula, which is likely a shared dependency with some other program I installed as root.</description></item><item><title>Cheatsheet</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/cheatsheet/</guid><description>I think most people hate writing bash scripts. Bash took the concept of syntactic sugar and thought, &amp;ldquo;what if syntactic pain&amp;rdquo;?
So anyways, this is a collection of tricks for making sure your thing stays running in a non-forkbomb sort of way and some other stuff too.
Persistence/application check
if ! pgrep -f &amp;#34;myth.py&amp;#34; &amp;gt;/dev/null; then setsid --fork python3 /var/atlassian/application-data/bitbucket/bin/myth.py &amp;lt;/dev/null &amp;amp;&amp;gt;/dev/null &amp;amp; fi Restart autossh if one or both connections are down</description></item><item><title>Edit the Blog with Obsidian</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/edit-with-obsidian/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/edit-with-obsidian/</guid><description>Maybe I will use this more if I can edit it with Obsidian. Let&amp;rsquo;s see!
In order to edit with Obsidian, I took some inspiration from this:
https://github.com/vinibaggio/obsblog-template
Where the basic idea is just to use Obsidian Git to push changes to the repository. No idea how well this works on mobile, and it seems to have the drawback that Obsidian still can&amp;rsquo;t edit .md files by default.
Obsidian Git&amp;rsquo;s documentation is useless.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Debugging</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/k8s-debugging/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/k8s-debugging/</guid><description>Print kubectl logs from deployment or scaled-job kubectl logs -l scaledjob.keda.sh/name=httpx-scaledjob --follow --max-log-requests 500 Creating an Ubuntu Pod cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f - apiVersion: v1 kind: Pod metadata: name: ubuntu labels: app: ubuntu spec: containers: - image: ubuntu command: - &amp;#34;sleep&amp;#34; - &amp;#34;604800&amp;#34; imagePullPolicy: IfNotPresent name: ubuntu restartPolicy: Always EOF kubectl exec -it ubuntu -- /bin/bash
Privileged with service account and host networking cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f - apiVersion: v1 kind: Pod metadata: name: ubuntu labels: app: ubuntu spec: hostNetwork: true serviceAccountName: httpx-service-account containers: - image: ubuntu command: - &amp;#34;sleep&amp;#34; - &amp;#34;604800&amp;#34; imagePullPolicy: IfNotPresent name: ubuntu securityContext: privileged: true restartPolicy: Always EOF maybe only try this at home kids</description></item><item><title>Obsidian Livesync Setup (WIP)</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/livesync-setup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/livesync-setup/</guid><description>install docker compose
sudo curl -L &amp;#34;https://github.com/docker/compose/releases/download/v2.20.1/docker-compose-linux-x86_64&amp;#34; -o /usr/local/bin/docker-compose sudo chmod +x /usr/local/bin/docker-compose https://github.com/vrtmrz/self-hosted-livesync-server</description></item><item><title>Obsidian Plugins</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/obsidian-plugins/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/obsidian-plugins/</guid><description>List of essential plugins
Obsidian LiveSync obsidian://show-plugin?id=obsidian-livesync
Easy Setup URI (pls do not crack) Click Here
Obsidian Git obsidian://show-plugin?id=obsidian-git
VSCode Editor obsidian://show-plugin?id=vscode-editor
Make sure to add toml to your file extensions list and enable &amp;ldquo;Detect all file extensions&amp;rdquo; in Files &amp;amp; Links.</description></item><item><title>Selenium Grid RCE - Chrome on Linux</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/selenium-grid-rce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 13:41:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/selenium-grid-rce/</guid><description>Selenium is an awesome tool that you can use to completely drive a web browser through a nice and simple python interface. There&amp;rsquo;s lots of cool possibilities to use this for red teaming, however the simplest is that it can provide a trivial vector for RCE when unauthenticated.
There are several publicly available exploits for Selenium Grid, however during testing I found that most of them were either low quality or do not work on unix environments due to the executable filesystem permission.</description></item><item><title>Install Docker On Ubuntu or Pop</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 13:05:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/docker/</guid><description>Simple copy and paste to install docker on Ubuntu as of 9/12/22
sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install \ ca-certificates \ curl \ gnupg \ lsb-release sudo mkdir -p /etc/apt/keyrings curl -fsSL https://download.docker.com/linux/ubuntu/gpg | sudo gpg --dearmor -o /etc/apt/keyrings/docker.gpg echo \ &amp;#34;deb [arch=$(dpkg --print-architecture) signed-by=/etc/apt/keyrings/docker.gpg] https://download.docker.com/linux/ubuntu \ $(lsb_release -cs) stable&amp;#34; | sudo tee /etc/apt/sources.list.d/docker.list &amp;gt; /dev/null sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install docker-ce docker-ce-cli containerd.io docker-compose-plugin https://docs.docker.com/engine/install/ubuntu/</description></item><item><title>Executing Code on Python Package Installs - Malicious Pypi</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/malicious-pypi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 08:39:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/malicious-pypi/</guid><description>Foreword Multiple researchers in the community have given dependency confusion and other supply chain attacks a bad name recently. While there are very valid reasons to perform this attack, please do not pollute pypi or any other package manager with typosquatting, stolen code, or other non-targetted attacks in the name of security research. It&amp;rsquo;s no different than spreading malware. The point has been made. Please be responsible.
Executing code on package install While most python packages are distributed as wheels, the &amp;ldquo;binary&amp;rdquo; distribution format, Pypi also enables developers to distribute their package as source distributions (or sdist).</description></item><item><title>Edit the Blog</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/edit-the-blog/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 16:18:56 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/edit-the-blog/</guid><description>clone the blog with
git clone --recurse-submodules git@github.com:evillogic/infosec-blog.git create a new page with
hugo new &amp;lt;page-name&amp;gt;.md Building the pages is simply hugo, however due to submodule behavior we need to first checkout the master submodule branch. You can then simply navigate to the public directory and push the change.
The workflow looks something like this:
build the new content the new content is written to the public folder, a submodule pointing to evillogic/evillogic.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 16:59:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/about/</guid><description>My name is Kaz, I am currently red team for and love to do research on security topics. I think we do too much work finding issues in specific things, and not enough work making it easy to find and prevent the issues. Let&amp;rsquo;s work on that.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Burp Suite on Android 7/8/9/10</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/burp-android-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/burp-android-tutorial/</guid><description>NOTE: You will need a rooted phone for this tutorial.
If you’ve recently tried to use Burp for Android versions Nougat or higher, you’ll know that many apps have simply stopped functioning through Burp.
Most notably, apps like the play store complain about not having internet, even though you can connect to HTTP sites and probably get a cert error going to HTTPS sites, but it still works.
Even after you resolve these errors by installing your certificate in the system store, HTTPS still will not function due to Burp’s cert having an invalid length of time.</description></item><item><title>An LDAP Exfil Technique</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/ldap-exfil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/ldap-exfil/</guid><description>Recently I’ve been looking a lot at data exfiltration techniques in general, especially techniques that allow you to bypass network access controls and escape from PCI environments.
I recently discovered a little trick that you can use to traverse network boundaries and obfuscate the source of your data via LDAP, which means that as long as the environment uses active directory and there’s a device (such as a primary domain controller) that has the ability to cross network boundaries, you can leverage this technique to use any Windows box as a proxy between two boxes you control.</description></item><item><title>Windows Hardening Stuff</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/windows-hardening/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/notes/windows-hardening/</guid><description>This is a random list of notes for Windows Hardening
Against Responder
“Turn off multicast name resolution” Enabled
Don’t need SMB? Turn it off
From Services.msc Disable and Stop “Server” AKA LanmanServer. Restart.
Need SMB but worried about Eternal Blue?
Set-SmbServerConfiguration -EnableSMB1Protocol $false
Fuck it why not just turn it all off for good measure?
Set-SmbServerConfiguration -EnableSMB2Protocol $false</description></item><item><title>Bypassing Windows Defender and AMSI 2019 With Privileges</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/amsi-bypass-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/amsi-bypass-2019/</guid><description>These steps assume you have access to powershell with admin rights. For the record, I’m not sure if this will work on a domain joined machine where conflicting policies may have been set. The AMSI script works by patching the AMSI DLL in memory, which means it’s not persistent and does not require privileges. The Defender command changes a registry value, which means it is persistend and it also requires privileges.</description></item><item><title>Mounting a Shared Folder in Kali and VMware Workstation/Player 2019</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/vmware-shared-folder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/vmware-shared-folder/</guid><description>I hate that I have to write this, but a lot of the solutions out there are really old and misleading. I’ve spent hours before just trying to get this to work. This method works with Kali 2019.3, and the day of this writing is 9/13/2019.
First install the relevant tools:
sudo apt install -y open_vm_tools open_vm_tools_desktop
Then make sure you share your folder through VM -&amp;gt; Settings -&amp;gt; Options tab and then set it to “Always Enabled”</description></item><item><title>Git Setup CheatSheet</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/git-cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/git-cheatsheet/</guid><description>Setting up your user git config --global user.name &amp;quot;Your name here&amp;quot;
git config --global user.email &amp;quot;your_email@example.com&amp;quot;
add your ssh key (in ~/.ssh/id_rsa.pub) to your github account
ssh -T git@github.com
credit to kbroman
Setting up a new repository Create an empty repository on github and clone it using the git address specified near the top of the page
git clone git@github.com:username/new_repo.gitg cd new_repo git commit -m &amp;quot;First Commit!&amp;quot;
git push -u origin master</description></item><item><title>Kali Proxmark Quick Setup</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/kali-proxmark-setup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/kali-proxmark-setup/</guid><description>This massive one-liner should work to install all the source.
sudo apt install -y p7zip git build-essential libreadline5 libreadline-dev libusb-0.1-4 libusb-dev libqt4-dev perl pkg-config wget libncurses5-dev gcc-arm-none-eabi libpcsclite-dev &amp;amp;&amp;amp; git clone https://github.com/Proxmark/proxmark3.git &amp;amp;&amp;amp; cd proxmark3 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; make clean &amp;amp;&amp;amp; make all
Now install the bootloader.
./client/flasher /dev/ttyACM0 -b bootrom/obj/bootrom.elf
Now install the full image. I encountered issues flashing the full image wherein my Proxmark3 RD4 had both A &amp;amp; C lights lit red, and it would not reconnect.</description></item><item><title>Overriding Windows TrustedInstaller Permissions</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/windows-trustedinstaller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/windows-trustedinstaller/</guid><description>tl;dr
For a single file, all you have to do is:
takeown /F C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FILE
icacls C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FILE /grant Administrators:F
For an entire directory, it’s a bit longer:
takeown /F C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER
takeown /F C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER /r /d y
icacls C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER /grant Administrators:F
icacls C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER /grant Administrators:F /t
Basically, this can be used to modify and overwrite Windows’s system files and other things you’re not supposed to touch. This can also be done from the GUI by assigning yourself to be the owner of the file, applying the change, closing the window, opening the permissions again, elevating to admin, and finally setting the permissions you would like.</description></item><item><title>Bypassing Windows Defender with the Windows Subsystem for Linux!</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/subsystem-defender-bypass/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/subsystem-defender-bypass/</guid><description>After watching BHIS’s Sacred Cash Cow Tipping 2020 I was inspired to try out a few of the techniques BHIS demoed, and this is a pretty fun and odd one.
There’s a few issues with WSL that make it a really poor choice for hacking without some configurations. The interesting one here is that WSL does not use VHDs or emulate linux filesystems, in fact, you can navigate to %AppData%/Local/Packages/$LinuxDistro/LocalState/rootfs and interact with the entire filesystem.</description></item><item><title>Making this blog – Expectations</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/expectations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/expectations/</guid><description>This blog is totally gonna get pwned within 24 hours of Google indexing it.
Things you can expect from this blog:
Posts about beginners’ and maybe advanced cyber security Every single bug in discord.py Musings on esoteric game systems Delusions about Game Development A splash of Personal Development The World of Worldbuilding Maybe some magic? (not the TCG) Things you can’t expect from this blog:
Common sense Pop culture The revelation that I am secretly Bruce Schneier</description></item></channel></rss>