<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on infosec blog</title>
    <link>https://evillogic.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on infosec blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2022 Kaz Bishop</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 13:41:09 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://evillogic.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Selenium Grid RCE - Chrome on Linux</title>
      <link>https://evillogic.github.io/posts/selenium-grid-rce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 13:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evillogic.github.io/posts/selenium-grid-rce/</guid>
      <description>Selenium is an awesome tool that you can use to completely drive a web browser through a nice and simple python interface. There&amp;rsquo;s lots of cool possibilities to use this for red teaming, however the simplest is that it can provide a trivial vector for RCE when unauthenticated.
There are several publicly available exploits for Selenium Grid, however during testing I found that most of them were either low quality or do not work on unix environments due to the executable filesystem permission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Executing Code on Python Package Installs - Malicious Pypi</title>
      <link>https://evillogic.github.io/posts/malicious-pypi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 08:39:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evillogic.github.io/posts/malicious-pypi/</guid>
      <description>Foreword Multiple researchers in the community have given dependency confusion and other supply chain attacks a bad name recently. While there are very valid reasons to perform this attack, please do not pollute pypi or any other package manager with typosquatting, stolen code, or other non-targetted attacks in the name of security research. It&amp;rsquo;s no different than spreading malware. The point has been made. Please be responsible.
Executing code on package install While most python packages are distributed as wheels, the &amp;ldquo;binary&amp;rdquo; distribution format, Pypi also enables developers to distribute their package as source distributions (or sdist).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
