<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on wooper blog</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on wooper blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 Kaz Bishop</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.kazam.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cracking Legacy Passwords</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/cracking-passwords-aws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/cracking-passwords-aws/</guid><description>The advent of cloud computing and ephemeral compute has to be one of the greatest things that ever happened to password cracking. Gone are the days of needing to buy an insane GPU rig, spend many to hours build it out, and have it be obsolete by the end of the year.</description></item><item><title>Selenium Grid RCE - Chrome on Linux</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/selenium-grid-rce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 13:41:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/selenium-grid-rce/</guid><description>Selenium is an awesome tool that you can use to completely drive a web browser through a nice and simple python interface. There&amp;rsquo;s lots of cool possibilities to use this for red teaming, however the simplest is that it can provide a trivial vector for RCE when unauthenticated.</description></item><item><title>Executing Code on Python Package Installs - Malicious Pypi</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/malicious-pypi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 08:39:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/malicious-pypi/</guid><description>Foreword Multiple researchers in the community have given dependency confusion and other supply chain attacks a bad name recently. While there are very valid reasons to perform this attack, please do not pollute pypi or any other package manager with typosquatting, stolen code, or other non-targetted attacks in the name of security research.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Burp Suite on Android 7/8/9/10</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/burp-android-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/burp-android-tutorial/</guid><description>NOTE: You will need a rooted phone for this tutorial.
If you’ve recently tried to use Burp for Android versions Nougat or higher, you’ll know that many apps have simply stopped functioning through Burp.
Most notably, apps like the play store complain about not having internet, even though you can connect to HTTP sites and probably get a cert error going to HTTPS sites, but it still works.</description></item><item><title>An LDAP Exfil Technique</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/ldap-exfil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/ldap-exfil/</guid><description>Recently I’ve been looking a lot at data exfiltration techniques in general, especially techniques that allow you to bypass network access controls and escape from PCI environments.
I recently discovered a little trick that you can use to traverse network boundaries and obfuscate the source of your data via LDAP, which means that as long as the environment uses active directory and there’s a device (such as a primary domain controller) that has the ability to cross network boundaries, you can leverage this technique to use any Windows box as a proxy between two boxes you control.</description></item><item><title>Bypassing Windows Defender and AMSI 2019 With Privileges</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/amsi-bypass-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/amsi-bypass-2019/</guid><description>These steps assume you have access to powershell with admin rights. For the record, I’m not sure if this will work on a domain joined machine where conflicting policies may have been set. The AMSI script works by patching the AMSI DLL in memory, which means it’s not persistent and does not require privileges.</description></item><item><title>Mounting a Shared Folder in Kali and VMware Workstation/Player 2019</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/vmware-shared-folder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/vmware-shared-folder/</guid><description>I hate that I have to write this, but a lot of the solutions out there are really old and misleading. I’ve spent hours before just trying to get this to work. This method works with Kali 2019.3, and the day of this writing is 9/13/2019.</description></item><item><title>Git Setup CheatSheet</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/git-cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/git-cheatsheet/</guid><description>Setting up your user git config --global user.name &amp;quot;Your name here&amp;quot;
git config --global user.email &amp;quot;your_email@example.com&amp;quot;
add your ssh key (in ~/.ssh/id_rsa.pub) to your github account
ssh -T git@github.com
credit to kbroman
Setting up a new repository Create an empty repository on github and clone it using the git address specified near the top of the page</description></item><item><title>Kali Proxmark Quick Setup</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/kali-proxmark-setup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/kali-proxmark-setup/</guid><description>This massive one-liner should work to install all the source.
sudo apt install -y p7zip git build-essential libreadline5 libreadline-dev libusb-0.1-4 libusb-dev libqt4-dev perl pkg-config wget libncurses5-dev gcc-arm-none-eabi libpcsclite-dev &amp;amp;&amp;amp; git clone https://github.com/Proxmark/proxmark3.git &amp;amp;&amp;amp; cd proxmark3 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; make clean &amp;amp;&amp;amp; make all</description></item><item><title>Overriding Windows TrustedInstaller Permissions</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/windows-trustedinstaller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/windows-trustedinstaller/</guid><description>tl;dr
For a single file, all you have to do is:
takeown /F C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FILE
icacls C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FILE /grant Administrators:F
For an entire directory, it’s a bit longer:
takeown /F C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER
takeown /F C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER /r /d y
icacls C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER /grant Administrators:F
icacls C:\FULL_PATH_TO_FOLDER /grant Administrators:F /t</description></item><item><title>Bypassing Windows Defender with the Windows Subsystem for Linux!</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/subsystem-defender-bypass/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/subsystem-defender-bypass/</guid><description>After watching BHIS’s Sacred Cash Cow Tipping 2020 I was inspired to try out a few of the techniques BHIS demoed, and this is a pretty fun and odd one.
There’s a few issues with WSL that make it a really poor choice for hacking without some configurations.</description></item><item><title>Making this blog – Expectations</title><link>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/expectations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kazam.io/posts/expectations/</guid><description>This blog is totally gonna get pwned within 24 hours of Google indexing it.
Things you can expect from this blog:
Posts about beginners’ and maybe advanced cyber security Every single bug in discord.py Musings on esoteric game systems Delusions about Game Development A splash of Personal Development The World of Worldbuilding Maybe some magic?</description></item></channel></rss>